<resources>
    <string name="app_name">XLine</string>
    <string name="title_home">Design</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Calculate</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Explore</string>
    <string-array name="text">
        <item>Click to get</item>
        <item>The complete NESIS standard</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">Calculate</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">obtain some of the major line considerations</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_calculator">Calculator</string>

    <string name="general_provisionse">
        The standards, as outlined herein, deal with requirements, compulsory procedures and
practices necessary for overhead transmission line construction in the Nigerian
Electricity Supply Industry. It is designed to meet service reliability, safe operation and
maintenance of transmission lines. Such transmission lines shall be capable of
withstanding expected electrical and climatic loads while maintaining design
consistency between strengths of line components. There shall be a written approval
granted by NERC prior to the construction of transmission lines. The transmission
line shall be designed to meet the following fundamental requirements and shall comply
with the provisions of IEC 60826 standard:
i. Ensure reliable and safe power transmission capability
ii. Reduce the probability of uncontrollable propagation of failures (failure containment)
iii. Ensure safe construction and maintenance conditions
    </string>
    <string name="right_of_ways">
    The Right of Way (RoW) is the distance of any structure from the middle conductors of
overhead power lines of any voltage level. The RoW shall be as indicated in the table 3.1.
</string>

    <string name="overhead_transmission_conductors">
        The standards, as outlined herein, deal with requirements, compulsory procedures and
practices necessary for overhead transmission line construction in the Nigerian
Electricity Supply Industry. It is designed to meet service reliability, safe operation and
maintenance of transmission lines. Such transmission lines shall be capable of
withstanding expected electrical and climatic loads while maintaining design
consistency between strengths of line components. There shall be a written approval
granted by NERC prior to the construction of transmission lines. The transmission
line shall be designed to meet the following fundamental requirements and shall comply
with the provisions of IEC 60826 standard:
i. Ensure reliable and safe power transmission capability
ii. Reduce the probability of uncontrollable propagation of failures (failure containment)
iii. Ensure safe construction and maintenance conditions
    </string>


    <string name="general_provisions">
        The standards, as outlined herein, deal with requirements, compulsory procedures and
practices necessary for overhead transmission line construction in the Nigerian
Electricity Supply Industry. It is designed to meet service reliability, safe operation and
maintenance of transmission lines. Such transmission lines shall be capable of
withstanding expected electrical and climatic loads while maintaining design
consistency between strengths of line components. There shall be a written approval
granted by NERC prior to the construction of transmission lines. The transmission
line shall be designed to meet the following fundamental requirements and shall comply
with the provisions of IEC 60826 standard:
i. Ensure reliable and safe power transmission capability
ii. Reduce the probability of uncontrollable propagation of failures (failure containment)
iii. Ensure safe construction and maintenance conditions
    </string>

    <string name="properties_of_electrical_conductors">
    Minimum Tensile Strength:
    Overhead transmission conductors – including overhead ground wires but excluding
    the case where they are cables – shall be stranded wires with a tensile strength no less
    than 10kN/m.
    Bare Conductors:
    Bare conductors and overhead ground wires (including overhead ground wires
    containing optical fibre cables) that are used for transmission lines shall conform to the
    following requirements:
    Properties of Solid Wires
    Solid wires (hard-drawn copper wire, hard-drawn aluminium wire, galvanized steel wire,
    aluminium alloy wire, etc.) which compose an electrical conductor, shall have
    conductivity and tensile strength not lower than the values specified in the IEC
    standards IEC60028, 60889, 60888, 61232, and 60104.
    </string>

    <string name="insulation_of_conductors">
Mechanical Strength of Insulators for Overhead Transmission Lines
a. Assumed Load
        The assumed loads to be used for calculating the strength of insulator devices for
overhead transmission lines shall conform to the following requirements:
i. Vertical Load: The vertical load shall be the sum of the weight of electrical conductors,
the weight of insulator devices and the vertical component of force generated by the
assumed maximum tension of the electrical conductors.
ii. Horizontal Transverse Load: The horizontal transverse load shall be the sum of the
wind pressure loads of electrical conductors and insulator devices and the horizontal
component of load generated by the assumed maximum tension of the electrical
conductors.
        iii. Assumed Maximum Tension of Transmission Conductors: The assumed maximum
tension of the transmission conductor under the composite load of the vertical load
generated by the weight of the electrical conductor and the horizontal load generated
by the horizontal wind pressure stipulated in Table 3.3.1a at the average temperature in
the area.
    </string>

    <string name="dielectric_strength">
Clearance between Supporting Structures and Electrical Conductors
The clearance between overhead transmission conductors (excluding cables) and their
supporting structures, cross arms or guys (pole braces) shall not be less than the
values shown in Table 3.4.1 even when the electrical conductor sways by a wind
velocity of about 20m/s.
a. Dielectric Strength of Insulators
The insulators to be used for overhead transmission lines shall have the dielectric
strength that has been verified in the wet power-frequency voltage test specified in
IEC60383-1 or other equivalent IEC tests.
        b. Dielectric Strength Test
Where the operational voltage to ground is applied between the overhead transmission
line and the ground continuously for ten (10) minutes to test the dielectric strength (in
conformity with IEC60038) before the commencement of operation, the transmission
line shall withstand such a test standard.
c. In case where cables are used for overhead transmission lines, the test shall conform
to subsection 3.8.1.1. get it from the original NESIS standard
    </string>

    Where electric circuits cross at mid-span positions, the following conditions shall apply
    a. The circuit of the higher voltage shall always cross over the circuit of the lower voltage;
    b. No circuit shall cross at an angle of less than 30 degrees; and
    c. The minimum clearance between the nearest conductors of different circuits at the
    point of crossing, including "aerial" earth wire, shall not be less than that tabulated
    below PLUS the maximum design sag of the conductor of the lower circuit at the point
    of crossing.

    <string name="support_structures">
    Steel Structural Members of Supporting Structures
    a. Fundamental Properties
    Flat steel, shaped steel, steel pipes, steel plates, steel bars and bolts which compose a
    steel tower or iron pole used for overhead transmission lines shall be appropriate ones
    as specified by ISO and SON.
    b. Thickness of Steel Members
    Shaped steel, steel pipes and steel plates to be used for steel tower or iron pole for
    overhead transmission lines shall have the thickness and other dimensions specified
    below:
    i. Minimum thickness of shaped steel to be used as:
    a. Main post member of an iron pole (in which a main member of a cross arm is included;
    the same shall apply hereafter in this section) shall have the thickness of 4mm.
    b. Main post member of a steel tower shall have the thickness of 5mm.
    c. Other structural members shall have the thickness of 3mm.
    ii. Minimum thickness of steel pipes to be used as:
    a. Main post member of an iron pole shall have the thickness of 2mm.
    b. Main post member of a steel tower shall have the thickness of 2.4mm.
    c. Other structural members shall have the thickness of 1.6mm.
    iii. Slenderness ratio of steel members
    The slenderness ratio of a compression member shall be no more than 200 for those to
    be used as a main post member and no more than 220 for compression members other
    than main post members (excluding those used as auxiliary members) and no more
    than 250 for those used as auxiliary members.
    iv. Minimum thickness of steel plates
    The thickness shall be no less than 1mm.
    </string>

    <string name="regulations_for_installation">
        Clearance between Overhead Ground Wires and Electrical Conductors
    Where electric circuits cross at mid-span positions, the following conditions shall apply
        a.The circuit of the higher voltage shall always cross over the circuit of the lower voltage;
    b. No circuit shall cross at an angle of less than 30 degrees; and
    c. The minimum clearance between the nearest conductors of different circuits at the
    point of crossing, including "aerial" earth wire, shall not be less than that tabulated
    below PLUS the maximum design sag of the conductor of the lower circuit at the point
    of crossing.
        Height of Overhead Transmission Conductors and Limitation of Span
a. The height above ground of any electric line under the most adverse operating
conditions shall not, except with the written authority of NERC, be less than the height
appropriate to the system voltage and situations tabulated in Table 3.6.2.
b. Fully insulated service lines operating at a voltage not exceeding 400Volts may be
terminated on buildings at a height of not less than 2.7 m from ground level provided
that the street clearance at any point of its span is not less than 5.8 m.
        Clearance between Plants and Overhead Transmission Conductors
The clearance between any overhead transmission conductor and any plant shall not
be less than the value specified in the Table 3.6.3. The clearance shall be
secured to provide for the occurrence of such case that the electrical conductor dips at
the maximum design operating temperature or sways in the wind.
    </string>
    <string name="restriction_in_urban">
        No overhead transmission line shall be installed in urban areas or other densely
populated and built-up areas.
The restrictions above shall not apply where the nominal voltage of the overhead
transmission line is not more than 132kV and the electrical conductors are cables or the
installation is carried out according to the following requirements:
a. Strength of electrical conductor
The strength of electrical conductor shall conform to Table 3.6.4(a).
     b. Limitation of Span
The length of span of overhead transmission lines shall conform to Table 3.6.4(b).
        c. Height of electrical conductor above the ground
The height of overhead transmission conductors above the ground shall be not less
than the value specified in Table 3.6.4(c) below. The height shall be secured to provide
for the occurrence of such case that the electrical conductor sag at the maximum
design operating temperature.
This shall not apply to overhead transmission lines for a span connecting the yard of a
power plant, substation or similar place to the outside.
        d. Indication of danger
Supporting structures shall be provided with an indication of danger in a location where
it is easily read. This shall not apply when insulated conductors are used for overhead
transmission lines with a nominal voltage less than or equal to 33kV.
e. Definition of an Urban Area or Other Densely Built-up Area
An urban area or other densely built-up area shall be defined according to the buildingto-
land ratio specified in Table 3.6.4(d)

    </string>
    <string name="regulations_for_side_by_side_installation">
    Alternative provision
    a. Where the condition of Clause 3.6.2(check from original NESIS standard) cannot be met, the line shall be erected so that the
    minimum horizontal distance in meters of the nearest conductor in still air is not less
    than-
    (Conductor sag at maximum design temperature PLUS length of suspension insulator
    string) PLUS B, where "B" is a constant dependent on the voltage between phases of
    the conductors of the line-
    415Volts - 11,000 Volts 2.4 meters
    33,000 Volts 3.0 meters
    132,000 Volts 4.0 meters
    330,000 Volts 6.0 meters
    Over 330,000 Volts 9.0 meters
    b. Where the conductors of the circuit are fully insulated the constant "B" may be reduced
    by 50%.
    c. In the case of specially designed fully insulated serial cables clearance to buildings may
    be reduced at the discretion of NERC.
    d. No building or other structure shall be erected under or adjacent to an electric line
    without adhering to the provisions of this standard.
    </string>
    <string name="installtation_with_db_conductors">
    3.7.1.1 Installation with Distribution Conductors
    a. When overhead transmission conductors with a nominal voltage higher than 33kV and
    overhead distribution conductors are installed on the same supporting structure, the
    installation shall be carried out in accordance with the requirements of Chapter 5.
    The electrical conductor with a higher voltage shall be installed above the electrical
    conductor with a lower voltage, using separate cross arms.
    i. Clearance
    The clearance between any overhead transmission conductor and any overhead
    distribution conductor shall be not shorter than the values specified in Table 3.7.1.1(a)
    ii. Strength of overhead distribution conductors
    Overhead distribution conductors shall be any of those specified in the following items
    except for cases where cables are used:
    a. Those with a tensile strength no less than 5 kN where the span of the overhead
    distribution conductor is not longer than 50m
    b. Those with a tensile strength no less than 8 kN where the span of the overhead
    distribution conductor is longer than 50m.
    c. Overhead transmission conductors with a nominal voltage over 33kV but below 132kV
    and low-voltage overhead distribution conductors shall not be installed on the same
    supporting structure.
        When overhead transmission conductors with a nominal voltage over 33kV but below
132kV and medium-voltage overhead distribution conductors are installed on the same
supporting structure, the installation shall be carried out in accordance with the
following requirements:
i. Position of installing electrical conductors
Overhead transmission conductors shall be installed above overhead distribution
conductors using separate cross arms. This shall not apply where such overhead
distribution conductor is installed together with overhead distribution conductor for the
SWER system.
ii. Strength of overhead transmission conductors
The overhead transmission conductors shall be the stranded wires with a tensile
strength no less than 30 kN excluding the case where they are cables.
iii. Transmission line strengthening work
Overhead transmission lines shall be installed according to the provisions for type 2
transmission line strengthening work in Table 3.7.1.1(a).
iv. Clearance
d. The clearance between any overhead transmission conductor and any overhead
distribution conductor shall be no less than the values specified in Table 3.7.1.1(b).
    </string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor-y.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_inner_calculator">InnerCalculator</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>

    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>

    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="title_activity_design_activity">Design_activity</string>

    <string name="safetyfactor"> a. Assumed Load and Safety Factor:
Overhead transmission conductors and overhead ground wires (excluding cables, the
same applies hereafter in this section) shall be installed such that the tension shall
allow for a safety factor specified in (ii) below when they are subjected to the assumed
load specified in (i) below at an average ambient temperature of the test area.
1. Assumed Load: The assumed load for the calculation of tension of overhead
transmission conductors and overhead ground wires shall be the composite load of the
vertical loads and the horizontal loads specified as follows:
a. The vertical load shall be the weight of the electrical conductor.
b. The horizontal load shall be the horizontal wind pressure load of 790N per m2 of vertical
projected area of the electrical conductor.
2. Safety Factor: A safety factor of no less than 2.5 shall be applied to the tensile strength
(ultimate tensile strength; breaking strength) of overhead transmission conductors and
overhead ground wires.
b. Prevention of Damage due to Slight Wind Oscillation: Overhead transmission
conductors and overhead ground wires shall be installed so as not to suffer damage
from a slight wind oscillation.</string>
    <string name="insulators">The assumed loads to be used for calculating the strength of insulator devices for
overhead transmission lines shall conform to the following requirements:
1. Vertical Load: The vertical load shall be the sum of the weight of electrical conductors,
the weight of insulator devices and the vertical component of force generated by the
assumed maximum tension of the electrical conductors.
2. Horizontal Transverse Load: The horizontal transverse load shall be the sum of the
wind pressure loads of electrical conductors and insulator devices and the horizontal
component of load generated by the assumed maximum tension of the electrical
conductors.
    A safety factor of no less than 2.5 shall be applied to the insulator
devices for overhead transmission lines. The safety factor mentioned above shall be
obtained as follows:
a. Tension insulator device (Insulator device that anchors electrical conductors).
        safety factor = tensile break strength divided by the assumed maximum tension at support point.

ii. Suspension insulator device (Insulator device that electrical conductors are hung from).
        safety factor = tensile break strength divided by the composite load of transverse load and horizontal transverse load.

iii. Supporting insulator device safety factor = bending break strength divided by the horizoontal transverse load to vertical load
        applied perpendicular to axis of insulator device.
        The insulators to be used for the overhead transmission lines shall have the dielectric
strength that has been verified in the wet power-frequency voltage test specified in
IEC60383-1 or other equivalent IEC tests.
</string>
    <string name="firstclearance">Clearance between Overhead Ground Wires and Electrical Conductors.
Where electric circuits cross at mid-span positions, the following conditions shall apply
        a.The circuit of the higher voltage shall always cross over the circuit of the lower voltage;
b. No circuit shall cross at an angle of less than 30 degrees; and
c. The minimum clearance between the nearest conductors of different circuits at the
point of crossing, including "aerial" earth wire, shall not be less </string>
    <string name="secondclearance">Height of Overhead Transmission Conductors and Limitation of Span
a. The height above ground of any electric line under the most adverse operating
conditions shall not, except with the written authority of NERC, be less than </string>
    <string name="thirdclearance">b. Fully insulated service lines operating at a voltage not exceeding 400Volts may be
terminated on buildings at a height of not less than 2.7 m from ground level provided
that the street clearance at any point of its span is not less than 5.8 m.</string>
    <string name="doubleandsingle">the transmission circuit could be made single or double,
        The double circuit is usually more efficient and reliable,
        because it carries two separate threephase power on the same tower,
        hence can supply more power and when one set of three phase fail, the other can stand in, provided its capacity is not exceeded.
        Of course the double circuit is more expensive than the single circuit,
        because it requires more conductors and usually for double circuit,
        we usually have two ground wires </string>
    <string name="support_structure">
        Generally structures made of reinforced concrete, of even iron poles can be used, but the steel tower is reccommended. kindly explore clause 3.5.1 of NESIS to view requirements
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_ask_question"> </string>
    <string name="title_activity_basic">Basic</string>
</resources>
